<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2011-2014 Julien Nicoulaud <julien.nicoulaud@gmail.com>
  ~ Copyright (c) 2015 Vladimir Schneider <vladimir.schneider@gmail.com>
  ~
  ~ Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one
  ~ or more contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file
  ~ distributed with this work for additional information
  ~ regarding copyright ownership.  The ASF licenses this file
  ~ to you under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the
  ~ "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
  ~ with the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
  ~ software distributed under the License is distributed on an
  ~ "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
  ~ KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
  ~ specific language governing permissions and limitations
  ~ under the License.
  -->
<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin version="2" url="http://github.com/vsch/idea-multimarkdown">
  <id>com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown</id>
  <name>MultiMarkdown</name>
  <category>Custom Languages</category>
  <vendor url="http://github.com/vsch" email="vladimir.schneider@gmail.com">Vladimir Schneider</vendor>
  <version>1.0.21</version>
  <idea-version since-build="134.549"/>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

  <description><![CDATA[
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/html">
      <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vsch/idea-multimarkdown/master/assets/images/ScreenShot_source_preview_Small.png" alt="Screenshot">
      <p><b><a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown">Markdown</a> language support for IntelliJ platform.</b><br>
      With GitHub Flavoured Markdown extensions and GitHub style formatting. HTML Preview and HTML Text tabs</p>

      <p><b><span color="#2000C0">Feature requests and problem reports will be greatly appreciated!</span></b><br>
      <b>You can submit them at <a color="#30A0D8" href="https://github.com/vsch/idea-multimarkdown/issues"><u>vsch/idea-multimarkdown/issues</u></a> on GitHub.</b></p>

      <p><b><span color="#C00038">If you like this plugin then please leave a comment or rate it.</span></b><br>
      <b>You can do that on the JetBrains' </span> <a color="#30A0D8" href="https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/writeComment?pr=&pluginId=7896"><u>MultiMarkdown comment and rate</u></a> page</b></p>
    </div>
    ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <p>
    <b>1.0.21</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Change Settings for Custom CSS, now a checkbox controls if the text in custom CSS editor will be used as the stylesheet.</li>
        <li>: Fix clearing or loading new text into the CSS editor was not clearing caret position and selection</li>
        <li>: Add check box to specify that the custom CSS should be treated as a dark theme. Used to determine which Icons to use for Bullets/Task items</li>
        <li>: Add Focus Editor button to set focus to custom CSS editor without clearing selection or caret.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.20</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix Changing settings was not updating files. My apologies, it was a one-line cut/paste error during heavy refactoring of code.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.19</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix detection of files so that HTML Preview and HTML Text tabs will be displayed along with other plugins that handle Markdown</li>
        <li>: Add Application UI option to CSS theme. This will make HTML Preview match the Application UI setting: Default or Darcula</li>
        <li>: Add Custom CSS Editor in settings, now saves state of caret, selection and vertical scroll position when you apply or ok changes to make it more comfortable to experiment with custom CSS.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.18</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix darcula.css did not set background for body. Short documents would have white bottom</li>
        <li>: Fix bullets and numbers for loose list items did not line up with text</li>
        <li>: Add option to render bullet lists via icons. Color is set by CSS option: default/darcula but you get smaller bullets, with retina resolution, if your displays allows it.</li>
        <li>: Change HTML used for Preview Tab now has body.multimarkdown-preview instead of div#multimarkdown-preview. Otherwise, setting body background would affect IDEA tooltips and other dialog elements.</li>
        <li>: Change FileType to MultiMarkdown to avoid conflicts with other Markdown plugins for syntax highlighting</li>
        <li>: Change Settings Sample Text syntax highlighting is now always done with all optional extensions except Force Item Para and HTML Suppression to make all atttributes show up in the sample</li>
        <li>: Change default style sheet defines ordered list styles like GitHub: 1. - decimal, 2. lower-roman, 3. lower-alpha</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.17</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix styles for loose task list items spacing not being the same for first and following items</li>
        <li>: Fix task list items checkbox to be disabled, look closer to GitHub's</li>
        <li>: Add task item marker and task item marker (done) style attributes to settings</li>
        <li>: Change Custom CSS text area now uses CSS syntax highlighting and shows line numbers</li>
        <li>: Change Task list HTML conversion now done in pegdown</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.16</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix potential conflict with old Markdown plugin by prefixing all classes with MultiMarkdown</li>
        <li>: Change HTML Text tab is now an IDEA syntax highlighting text view</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.15</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Add Separate Setext header styles</li>
        <li>: Fix highlighting not working on version 14.1, due to plugin.xml change</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.14</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix Scratch files were not recognized as MultiMarkdown files</li>
        <li>: Fix Implement a Lexer so that expected IntelliJ functionality can be implemented</li>
        <li>: Fix Sample Text not working in Settings/Editor/Colors &amp; Fonts</li>
        <li>: Fix TODO's. Now working in comments like: &lt;!-- TODO: this is a todo item --&gt;</li>
        <li>: Add Option to trim trailing spaces from Markdown files. Previously it was disabled.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.13</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix Compound Definition list parsing. (pegdown) </li>
        <li>: Fix syntax highlighting for nested list elements would get out of sync with source. (pegdown) </li>
        <li>: Add Darcula default settings for syntax highlighting</li>
        <li>: Add Darcula CSS style sheet for HTML Preview</li>
        <li>: Add Force Loose List Items option to force a list item/definition term to be loose if it is more than a simple paragraph. (pegdown) </li>
        <li>: Add Header Space option to require a space after # for Atx Headers</li>
        <li>: Add Relaxed HRules to not require a blank line after a horizontal ruler, GitHub style</li>
        <li>: Change Tighten Definition list styles</li>
        <li>: Change Default Bullet list and Ordered list color to match Default Definition list color</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.12</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Add separate color setting for strikethrough, italic and bold lead/trail marker than the contained text</li>
        <li>: Add Smart character and Smart Quote color settings</li>
        <li>: Add default color definitions for Default color scheme. Darcula in the next few days.</li>
        <li>: Fix source range discrepancies for definition, list, html block, ... (pegdown)</li>
        <li>: Fix special character now only escaped with \ and takes selected extension options, ... (pegdown)</li>
        <li>: Fix table caption not syntax highlighting, (pegdown)</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.11</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix syntax highlighting broken since forking to a new plugin</li>
        <li>: Fix syntax highlighting for elements at the end of a file which missing a new line</li>
        <li>: Fix Setext headers with trailing blanks would not be recognized (pegdown)</li>
        <li>: Fix syntax highlighting to handle all permutations of strikeout, bold and italic</li>
        <li>: Add Table odd/even row and odd/even column syntax highlighting</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.10</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Change default style sheet to make fonts relative to the one and only set in px, clean up ignored attributes</li>
        <li>: Change plugin.xml to display description and change-notes in the settings dialog, plug-in info panel</li>
        <li>: Add Automatic generation of anchor links in headers in settings, pegdown ANCHORLINKS extension</li>
        <li>: Add 2x icons and dracula themed ones</li>
        <li>: Fixed default file extension was missing 'markdown'</li>
        <li>: Add HTML Text view to show generated HTML
          <ul>
            <li>Enable disable the HTML Text view in settings. Will need to reopen markdown files to take effect.</li>
            <li>Can show HTML as generated by pegdown or modified for idiosyncrasies of the HTMLEditorKit used to render the preview pane.</li>
          </ul>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.9</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fix null pointer exception when following a malformed link</li>
        <li>: Change document icon</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.8</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Add header space option, which requires a space between # and the title for headers GFM style</li>
        <li>: Fix fenced code without preceding blank line would become a code block embedded in the paragraph (pegdown)</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.7</b><br/>
      <ul>
        <li>: Fixed definition list parsing broken by last fix in pegdown</li>
        <li>: Fixed loose list items ignored the next blank line and were loose only if they contained other blocks in pegdown</li>
        <p>Now nested lists with paragraphs and code blocks are generated like GitHub but with better control over loose/tight lists.</p>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.6</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Fixed list parser bugs in pegdown-1.5.0 and included the fixed jar in the plug-in.
        <p>Now nested lists with paragraphs and code blocks are generated identical to GitHub.</p>
      </li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.5</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Change generated HTML to use span instead of del for strikethrough to control the look through CSS</li>
      <li>: Change max img width of 0 disables resizing</li>
      <li>: Fix tables had width=100%, removed</li>
      <li>: Add GitHub style task list items, ones starting with [], [ ] or [x] and associated settings options</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.4</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Change generated HTML to use span instead of del for strikethrough to control the look through CSS</li>
      <li>: Change max img width of 0 disables resizing</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.3</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Change generated HTML to use div instead of hr to control the look through CSS</li>
      <li>: Tweak document icon</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.2</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Change document icon</li>
      <li>: Fix use Application invokeLater, instead of SwingUtil</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.1</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Fork source into its own plug-in: MultiMarkdown</li>
      <li>: Add settings for update delay, img max-width</li>
      <li>: Add custom Css text area in settings and also ability to use defaults and load defaults for editing</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.0.0</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Limit images to 1000 pixels wide, resize if larger</li>
      <li>: Fix table to be striped</li>
    </ul>
    <b>0.9.8</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>: Fix no refresh on settings change</li>
      <li>: Update pegdown to 1.5.0 and parboiled to 1.1.7.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>0.9.7</b><br/>
    <ul>
      <li>Forked from <a href="https://github.com/nicoulaj/idea-markdown">idea-markdown</a></li>
    </ul>
    </p>
    <p>&nbsp;</p>
    ]]></change-notes>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <fileTypeFactory implementation="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.MultiMarkdownFileTypeFactory"/>
    <lang.syntaxHighlighterFactory key="MultiMarkdown" language="MultiMarkdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.highlighter.MultiMarkdownSyntaxHighlighterFactory"/>
    <colorSettingsPage implementation="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.highlighter.MultiMarkdownColorSettingsPage"/>
    <additionalTextAttributes scheme="Default" file="com/vladsch/idea/multimarkdown/colorSchemes/MultiMarkdownDefault.xml"/>
    <additionalTextAttributes scheme="Darcula" file="com/vladsch/idea/multimarkdown/colorSchemes/MultiMarkdownDarcula.xml"/>
    <fileEditorProvider implementation="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.editor.MultiMarkdownPreviewEditorProvider"/>
    <fileEditorProvider implementation="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.editor.MultiMarkdownHtmlEditorProvider"/>
    <lang.documentationProvider language="MultiMarkdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.documentation.MultiMarkdownDocumentationProvider"/>
    <lang.parserDefinition language="MultiMarkdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.parser.MultiMarkdownParserDefinition"/>
    <externalAnnotator language="MultiMarkdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.annotator.MultiMarkdownAnnotator"/>
    <spellchecker.support language="MultiMarkdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.spellchecking.MultiMarkdownSpellcheckingStrategy"/>
    <todoIndexer filetype="Markdown" implementationClass="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.todo.MultiMarkdownTodoIndexer"/>
    <applicationService serviceInterface="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.settings.MultiMarkdownGlobalSettings" serviceImplementation="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.settings.MultiMarkdownGlobalSettings"/>
    <applicationConfigurable instance="com.vladsch.idea.multimarkdown.settings.MultiMarkdownGlobalSettingsConfigurable"/>
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
